Guide to the Joy Golden Papers, 1956-2012 RL.00461
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1979-2005 and undated, 13 boxes
  - Audition tapes
    - Zephyr Hills Spring Water: Arnold and Stephanie. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
  - Commercials
    - AAA of Connecticut, 8 spots. 1987Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Abe Beame campaign spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Absolut Kurant. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - ADP (Automatic Data Processing): Barney Krupp; The Advisor; The Helper. 1992-1993Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV11)
    - ADP (Automatic Data Processing): Office Crisis; Home Late. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Alcon/Optizyme: Born Again Buddhist; Relationship. 1988-1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - Allie's BBQ Bar. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Alouette Cheese: Divorce; Sardines. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: 7 spots. 1991-1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV11)
    - AMTRAK. 1982 and undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 5 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Arizona Daily Star: Valley Girl. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - AT&T: Mother's Day; Moose Slippers. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - Atlanta Marriott Hotels: 40th Birthday; Tara. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Aux Bon Pain: Music tracks. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Avenue: Talk of the Avenue. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Babes R Us: In Labor; Baby Blues. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV11)
    - Beefsteak Charlie's: Party; Gaga. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Benihana Frozen Entrees: Translation/Samurai; Translation 2. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Bison Light Chip Dip: Mom Flipped. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield of N.J.: 15 spots. 1991-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Blue Star Foods/Dining Lite: 15th Anniversary; Office Rendezvous; Joan's Jewelry. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - Bryant Park Restoration: Marty's Friends; More Marty. 1987-1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Budweiser/LA Beer: 6 spots. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV11)
    - Burroughs Wellcome: HIV Testing. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - Caesar's: N.Y. Loves Caesar's; Pilot. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00, 3 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Caldor: Gifts for Her. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Caldor: Holiday campaign 17 spots. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 17:00 (Box AV11)
    - Caldor: Spanish spots. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV11)
    - Canada Dry: Too Jolly; You'll Freeze; Party; Prank Phone Call. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV11)
    - Candy Kisses Natural Lip Balm: She and He. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Capalbo's Gift Baskets: 8 spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV11)
    - Care Choices HMO: Clumsy; Double Dip Doughnuts. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Carefree Sugarless Gum: Airplane. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Carlsberg Beer: 7 spots. 1987-1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV11)
    - Carnival Air Lines: Catskills; New York Henny Youngman spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Catskills on Broadway: Doctor; Aunt Lil; Messenger. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - CBS Miami Channel 6 direct: 36 spots. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 26:00 (Box AV11)
    - Chanel Home Centers: They Helped Me/Gift. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - Cheerwine: 9 spots. 1988-1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV11)
    - Choice Care: If Your Head Hurts; Lake Ronkokomo. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV11)
    - Citicorp: Appliance Store; Restaurant. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Coca-Cola: Tall Tale; There Goes the Gang; The Telephone Call. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - Cohen's Fashion Optical: 5 spots. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV11)
    - Coors Beer: Cool Guy; Surfer. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Crabtree. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Creative Coalition: Environmental Bond Act. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Danskin: Starskin. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Deloitte & Touche: Annual Report. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Dunkin' Donuts: 17 spots. 1988-1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 17:00 (Box AV12)
    - Domestica Wine: Odysseus. 1983. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Brothel. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Convertible; Fees. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Hot Tub. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Smart Guy. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Tea Garden. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Tea Garden; Birthday. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Vacation; Tax Time. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - E-Loan: Wipe Out. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Eagle Snacks: 27 spots. 1983-1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 27:00 (Box AV12)
    - Eight O'Clock Coffee: 8 O'Clock Saturday; Dinner Party; All Nite DJ; Car Pool. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Elephant Malt Liquor: Stranger; Lawn Party; Med School; Surprise; Kloster. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV12)
    - Evian Spring Water: Restaurant; Singing Glasses; Her Secret. 1985-1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fair Auto Insurance PSA. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Family Counseling Services: Child Abuse; Family Violence; Lanie. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - First Florida Bank: Wedding; Fairy Tale; Ring; Liar. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - First Investors: The Thinker; Dentist; Dance Instructor; Home Movies. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fleischmann's Extra Light: Airplane. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Florida Power and Light: Young Couple; Kids. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Franklin Mint Classic Cars of the 50s: Ziggy and Dee Dee. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fresh Chef: Jordan; Mama's Boy. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: 5 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: 5 spots. 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: 7 spots. 1986 and undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: 10 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: 11 spots. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Audition tapes. 1988 and undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 5 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Business Meeting; Ha Ha Moo Moo; Happy Birthday. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Computer Boy; Breathless Afternoon. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Divorce; Lela; Shower. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Dotsie Hooper; Enid's Mother. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Enid and Galaxy; Stuart; Valley Girl IV. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Hot Tub Brunch; Valley Girl. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Lela. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Mrs. A. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 3 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Stuart. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Supermarket Sallie; Picnic; Party; Singles; Arnold's Mom (first produced spots). 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Uncle Hal. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Uncle Hal; Mrs. A. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 3 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Uncle Hal; Red Jogging Hat. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Valley Girl. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: Valley Girl 3, 4; Enid and Galaxy. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Fromagerie Bel (Frobel)/Laughing Cow: WNYC radio. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV12)
    - GEICO: Just Bought; Gonna Buy. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV12)
    - Golden Lager. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV12)
    - Goldstar Electronics: 7j spots. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV12)
    - Granada Rentals: Uncle John's Will; Cheapskate; Dial-a-Deal; Rent or Buy. 1984-1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Haagen-Dazs: Bradley Frumkis; Vanilla. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Haircare Harmony: Valley Girl. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Hebrew National Salami: Forgotten Salami; American Dreams; Renaissance Art; In the Poconos. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Indianapolis News/Indianapolis Star: Matchline Interview. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Interwest Bank: Nostalgia. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Jefferson Bank: Gift; Dr. Noodleman; Vacation. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - JobDirect.com: Chat; Party. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - JobDirect.com: Chat Room. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - JobDirect.com: Party. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - KABC-TV/Channel 7: Haunted Halloween; Shrink. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - KDKA-TV: Schmeckenbecker; Wrist TV; Eddie Santucci. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - KPIX-TV: 7 spots. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV12)
    - KTVT: Valley Girl. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - KYW-TV: Therapy Group; Shrink; Guy; Creatures of Habit; No More Talk. 1990-1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - La Cage Aux Folles: Dear Van Johnson; Jerry Herman; Arthur Laurents. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Ladies' Home Journal: 20 spots. 1986-1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV12)
    - Levi's Original 501: 13 spots. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV12)
    - Lifesavers: Wild Recipe. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV12)
    - Lightpath: Duffy. 2003. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Lillet Wine: Phil and Lil. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Live at 5/WNBC: Simmons; Slice. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Lysol Disinfectant: Who's Got It?. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Marcus James: Bartender Story; Jealous. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Mastercard: Haircut; Ad; Horoscope; Dump Truck. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV12)
    - Maxwell House Coffee: Gum; Sidewalk. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - MCI: Dude; Super Model; Lottery Commission; President. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - MCI: Princess; Boy/Linda's Father. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:30 (Box AV12)
    - Meadowlands Racetrack: Anniversary; Friday Night. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Medi-Quick: Sounds of Spring. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering: First Chance; Routine. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Mercury Radio Awards: Enid Returns; Harvey. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Midas: 7 spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV12)
    - Milkbone Dog Biscuits: 13 spots. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Money Magazine: Taxes; Anniversary; Dentist; Subscription; Hotel. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - Monmouth Park Racetrack: Opening Day; Proposal; Parasol; Diamond Jim Brady. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00, 3 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Morgan's Honey Mustard Salad Dressing: Bear. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Multiple Schlerosis Read-a-Thon: Midget. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - National Fuel: Range Dryer; Furnace. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV12)
    - NBC/Sears: Sue Simmons/Jack Cafferty; Len Berman; Al Roker. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - NEC Computers: Sales Guy. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Nescafe Specialty Coffees: 12 spots. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV12)
    - Network America: Chameleons. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - New York Style Bagel Chips: Anniversary; Cocktail Party; Frankie. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Nivea: 10 spots. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV12)
    - North Fork Bank: Beagles; Frobischer.1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - North Fork Bank: ET to DIMM?; Give Aways.1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - North Fork Bank: I Like Your Tie.1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - North Fork Bank: Memo; Relationships; Auditions.1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - North Fork Bank: No's; L.I. Whines.1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - North Fork Bank: Press Conference.1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - North Fork Bank: Relationships.1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Northwest Natural Gas: Cure for Procrastination; Mona. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Nutrisystem: Carmen Miranda. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - NY State Agriculture: Ink Blots; Clucking; Full Stomach. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Ohio Wines: NY NY; Lala Land; Georgia. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Old Tyme Soft Drinks: Exercise; Lulu; Lenny; Charlotte; Vacation. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - Opti-Free Lens Care: Mr. Right. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Partnership for a Drug-Free America: 9 spots. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV12)
    - Partnership for a Drug-Free America: Lanie's Wedding; Where Is the Baby?; Dedicated to Wayne; Mickey. 1987-1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV12)
    - Pealer's Flowers and More: Friends; 2000 Carats; Chance Meeting; Pop. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Pevely Dairy: 7 spots. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV12)
    - Physicians' Health Services: 12 spots. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV12)
    - Piat d'Or: Marguerite; Birthday; Older Man. 1983. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Pizza Hut: 19 spots. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 19:00 (Box AV12)
    - Precious Cheese: Theresa; Mrs. Capanari; Angela. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Ragu: Mom the Victor. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Ralston-Purina/Praise: Livin' on Love; Praise. 1982. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV12)
    - Rave Hair Products: Convertible. 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Regina Porter Clothes: Spiritual Awakening. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Restaurant Associates: Russians; Salon. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Rice Chex Juniors: Gippy. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Tough World; Why Advertise?; Tough Questions. 1991-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Why Advertise?; So Many Law Firms. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Roy Rogers: 6 spots. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV12)
    - Saks Fifth Avenue: Florida. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Savings Bank of Manchester: Pet Store. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Seagram's Fruit Coolers: 12 spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV12)
    - Sharp Electronics. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shell/Atlanta Re-Entry: Shell Be Comin'; Dipstick. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shell ETD Convenience Stores: Extra-Terrestrial; Member ETD; Transmogrifying Device; Band from Seattle. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shell Formulashell: 12 spots. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shell Rotella Oil: Bad Dream; Examination; Headache Remedy; Engine Doctor Superrigs. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shell Rotella Oil: Engine Doctor. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shell Rotella Oil: Rainy Night; Lady Trucker. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shell Rotella Oil: Secure; Dirty; Thick. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Shoe Town: Friends. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Short Circuit II: Girls; Boys. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV12)
    - Signal Mouthwash: Thydney; The Big It; Phone Call. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV12)
    - Sills and Company: Theatre Critic. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV12)
    - Smith Barney. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - Southern New England Telephone (SNET): 23 spots. 1985-1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 23:00 (Box AV13)
    - Southern New England Telephone (SNET): Lazlo. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - Sovran Bank: Loan; Convenience Store; Vending Machine. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV13)
    - Stressbusters: Man on the Run; Mrs. Warm Flash; Merva. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV13)
    - Sunkist: Dreaming. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - Supercharger: Wedding. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV13)
    - Sweet N' Low/Butter Buds: Cake Man; Tea Drinker; Ballpark Food. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV13)
    - Thighmaster Plus: Ruthie. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV13)
    - Tijuca Beer: Tijuca Intro; Inge Kraus; Fantastica; Elegansia. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV13)
    - Tri Star/Short Circuit II. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV13)
    - Tropical Freezes: Ma's Visit; Anniversary. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 11:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - UDV Multi-Brands: Super Bowl. 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - USA Network: Dream Car Giveaway; Lenny's Big Dream; Chester and Harold. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV13)
    - Valley National Bank: The Big Zero; Talking in Your Sleep. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV13)
    - Visa. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV13)
    - Vlasic Pickles/Wiejeske Wyroby/Milwaukee's Pickles: Billy Bob; State Fair. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV13)
    - Volvic Natural Spring Water: Shrinking World; Sounds of…; Rush Hour. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV13)
    - Wall Street Journal: Hot Dog Vendor; Announcement; Upward Mobility. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV13)
    - Warnaco: 29 spots.1991-1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 29:00 (Box AV13)
    - Warnaco: 8 spots. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV13)
    - Warnaco: Hurry to Macy's. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - Warnaco: Speedo Fitness Center/Into Fitness; Buy 2 Get 1 Free/Lunch; Christian Dior/Macy's/Bullock's. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV13)
    - Warnaco: Calvin Klein; Valentino. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV13)
    - Warnaco: Valentino. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV13)
    - Wee Three Records: Santa. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - Weight Watchers: Oompah. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV13)
    - Western Beef: 8 spots (English and Spanish). 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV13)
    - WFSB/Oprah Winfrey Show: Elsie Plodgett. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV13)
    - Whitehall/Hoffman La Roche Cough Syrup Abuse PSA: Mother. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - Wild Turkey: 7 spots. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV13)
    - Winkelman's: Coat and Sweater Sale; Spirit of the Season; Uncle Arthur. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV13)
    - Winkelman's: Gift List; Spirit of the Season; Uncle Arthur. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3;00 (Box AV13)
    - Winkelman's: Storewide 30% Sale. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
    - WKYC-TV/Entertainment Tonight: 8 spots. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV13)
    - WNBC: 15 spots. 1990-1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV13)
    - Workbench: What's a Workbench?. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV13)
    - WRC/Family Feud: Where's Ray Colmes? 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV13)
  - Compilations
    - Joy Radio Reel 1: 22 spots. 1979-1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 22:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 2: 25 spots. 1979-1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 25:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 3: 25 spots. 1979-1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 25:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 5: 18 spots. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 18:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 7: 31 spots. 1986-1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 31:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 8: 36 spots. 1986-1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 36:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 9: 36 spots. 1986-1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 36:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 10: 38 spots. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 38:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 11: 44 spots. 1987-1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 44:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 12: 29 spots. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 29:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 14: 26 spots. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 26:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 15: 25 spots. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 25:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 16: 18 spots. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 18:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 17: 18 spots. 1991-1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 18:00 (Box AV13)
    - Joy Radio Reel 18: 16 spots. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 16:00 (Box AV13)